Guide to the Josef Silverstein papers, [ca. 1950-1990]
Silverstein, Josef papers, [ca. 1950-1990]
- Series I. Correspondence and Research Files
  - Radio Free Asia (1 of 4) (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Radio Free Asia (1 of 4) (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Radio Free Asia (1 of 4) [tapes] (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Radio Free Burma (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Raman, N.V. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Research on Democracy; National University of Singapore (1 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Research on Democracy; National University of Singapore (2 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Research on Democracy; National University of Singapore (3 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Rethinking Political Development in Southeast Asia (1 of 6) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Rethinking Political Development in Southeast Asia (2 of 6) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Rethinking Political Development in Southeast Asia (3 of 6) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Rethinking Political Development in Southeast Asia (4 of 6) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Rethinking Political Development in Southeast Asia (5 of 6) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Rethinking Political Development in Southeast Asia (6 of 6) (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Richard, Carol A. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Richardson, Michael (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Richter, H.V.; Burma’s Rice Surpluses: Accounting for the Decline (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Salween, Watch; Dams Project (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Saya Daw U Rewatta Dhamma (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Schact. Chris (1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Schact. Chris (2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Schnapp, F.E. (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Schwartz, Eric (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Selith, Andrew (1 of 4) (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Selith, Andrew (2 of 4) (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Selith, Andrew (3 of 4) (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Selith, Andrew (4 of 4) (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Sein Win (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Sesser, Stan (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Shan (1 of 6) (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Shan (2 of 6) (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Shan (3 of 6) (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Shan (4 of 6) (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Shan (5 of 6) (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Shan (6 of 6) (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Shan Letters and Papers (1 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Shan Letters and Papers (2 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Shan Letters and Papers (3 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Shan Letters and Papers (4 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Shan Letters and Papers (5 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Shan Literature and Culture (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Shelby, Tucker (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Silverstein Articles (1 of 6) (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Silverstein Articles (2 of 6) (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Silverstein Articles (3 of 6) (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Silverstein Articles (4 of 6) (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Silverstein Articles (5 of 6) (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Silverstein Articles (6 of 6) (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Sivitz, Laura (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - SLORC at HRC Geneva (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - SLORC Speeches (1 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - SLORC Speeches (2 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - SLORC Speeches (3 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - SLORC Statement at U.N. (1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - SLORC Statement at U.N. (2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Smith, Alan (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Smith, Charles B. (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Smith, Martin (1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Smith, Martin (2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Snider, Eric (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Spar, Deborah (1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Spar, Deborah (2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - SPDC/SLORC Information (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - SPDC Convocation 2000 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - SPDC, Successor to SLORC (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Spiro, Melford E.; Marriage Papers (1 of 4) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Spiro, Melford E. (2 of 4) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Spiro, Melford E. (3 of 4) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Spiro, Melford E. (4 of 4) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Steinberg, David I. (1 of 7) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Steinberg, David I. (2 of 7) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Steinberg, David I. (3 of 7) (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Steinberg, David I.; 1978 Report on Resumption(4 of 7) (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Steinberg, David I.; 1978 Report on Resumption (5 of 7) (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Steinberg, David I.; 1998 World Bank Report (6 of 7) (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Steinberg, David I.; Aid Report on Burma, 1997 (7 of 7) (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Sukhumband (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Sutin Nophaket (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - SVLAK (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - U Thant (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Thant, Myint U. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Tin Maung Maung Than (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Tin Maung Win (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Turnell, Sean; Burma’s Economy (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Tyn Myunt U (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - U.N. Commission on Human Rights (1 of 16) (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - U.N. Commission on Human Rights (2 of 16) (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - U.N. Commission on Human Rights (3 of 16) (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - U.N. Commission on Human Rights (4 of 16) (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - U.N. Commission on Human Rights (5 of 16) (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - U.N. Commission on Human Rights (6 of 16) (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - U.N. Commission on Human Rights (7 of 16) (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - U.N. Commission on Human Rights (8 of 16) (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - U.N. Commission on Human Rights (9 of 16) (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - U.N. Commission on Human Rights (10 of 16) (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - U.N. Commission on Human Rights (11 of 16) (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - U.N. Commission on Human Rights (12 of 16) (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - U.N. Commission on Human Rights (13 of 16) (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - U.N. Commission on Human Rights (14 of 16) (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - U.N. Commission on Human Rights (15 of 16) (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - U.N. Commission on Human Rights (16 of 16) (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - U.N. General Assembly (1 of 7) (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - U.N. General Assembly (2 of 7) (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - U.N. General Assembly (3 of 7) (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - U.N. General Assembly (4 of 7) (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - U.N. General Assembly (5 of 7) (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - U.N. General Assembly (6 of 7) (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - U.N. General Assembly (7 of 7) (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - U.N. Secretary General (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - U.N. Secretary General (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - UNDP (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - United Nationalities (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - University of Mayland (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - UNOCAL Case (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Umemoto, S.H. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - UNLD (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - U.S.-Burma Relations; Research Project by Joseph Silverstein (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - U.S.-Burma Relations; Research Project by Joseph Silverstein (2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Congress (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Commission on Refugees (1 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - U.S. Commission on Refugees (2 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - U.S. Commission on Refugees (3 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - U.S. Department of State; Religious Freedom (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Department of State; Narcotics (2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - U.S. Government, Burma Narcotics (1 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - U.S. Government, Burma Narcotics (2 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - U.S. Government, Burma Narcotics (3 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - U.S. Government Congress (1 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - U.S. Government Congress (2 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - U.S. Government Congress (3 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - U.S. Government Congress Hearing; 1993-1995 (1 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - U.S. Government Congress Hearing; 1993-1995 (1 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - U.S. Government Congress Hearing; 1993-1995 (1 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - U.S. Government Department of State; Human Rights Report (1 of 6) (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - U.S. Government Department of State; Human Rights Report (2 of 6) (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - U.S. Government Department of State; Human Rights Report (3 of 6) (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - U.S. Government Department of State; Human Rights Report (4 of 6) (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - U.S. Government Department of State; Human Rights Report (5 of 6) (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - U.S. Government Department of State; Human Rights Report (6 of 6) (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - U.S. Government, Executive (1 of 6) (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - U.S. Government, Executive (2 of 6) (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - U.S. Government, Executive (3 of 6) (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - U.S. Government, Executive (4 of 6) (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - U.S. Government, Executive (5 of 6) (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - U.S. Government, Executive (6 of 6) (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Vale, Peter (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Various Manuscripts (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Various Manuscripts (2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Vum Son (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Wa (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Weideman, K. (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Weller, Marc (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Whittam, Daphne E. (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Whittam, Daphne E. (2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Wiant, Jon A. (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Wolff, Lester L. (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Women In Burma (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Woodard, Garry (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - World Bank (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - World Peace Foundation; Essays and Information for Book on Burma (1 of 7) (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - World Peace Foundation; Essays and Information for Book on Burma (2 of 7) (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - World Peace Foundation; Essays and Information for Book on Burma (3 of 7) (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - World Peace Foundation; Essays and Information for Book on Burma (4 of 7) (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - World Peace Foundation; Essays and Information for Book on Burma (5 of 7) (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - World Peace Foundation; Essays and Information for Book on Burma (6 of 7) (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - World Peace Foundation; Essays and Information for Book on Burma (7 of 7) (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Yang, Jackie (1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Yang, Jackie (2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Ye Myint (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Ying Yan Yanghwe (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Yukin Richard (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Zar Ni (1 of 8) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Zar Ni (2 of 8) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Zar Ni (3 of 8) (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Zar Ni (4 of 8) (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Zar Ni (5 of 8) (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Zar Ni (6 of 8) (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Zar Ni (7 of 8) (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Zar Ni (8 of 8) (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Zau Lat (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Zau Seng, George (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Zaw Oo (1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Zaw Oo (1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Zhang, Xizhen (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Burma Communism (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Burma Communist Party (1 of 6) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Burma Communist Party (2 of 6) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Burma Communist Party (3 of 6) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Burma Communist Party (4 of 6) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Burma Communist Party (5 of 6) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Burma Communist Party (6 of 6) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Burma Documents Pre-1962 (1 of 3) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Burma Documents Pre-1962 (2 of 3) [posters] (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Burma Documents Pre-1962 (3 of 3) (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Burma Election Data 1990 (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Burma Election Data 1990 (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Burma Ethnic Research Group (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Burma Funo (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Burma: HIV, AIDS (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Burma Lawyer Group (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Burma Lawyer Group: Aung Htoo (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Burma Lawyer Group: Aung Htoo (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Burma MAPS (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Burma Net Doug Steele (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Burma Orgis Apdnessier (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Burmese Election Data-1950 (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Burmese Election Data-1950 (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Burmese Election Data-1960 (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Burmese Election Data-1960 (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Commission for the Restoration of Democracy in Burma (1 of 5) (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Democracy in Burma (2 of 5) (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Democracy in Burma (3 of 5) (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Democracy in Burma (4 of 5) (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Democracy in Burma (5 of 5) (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Constitution Making (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Constitution Making (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - DAB and NDF (1 of 5) (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - DAB and NDF (2 of 5) (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - DAB and NDF (3 of 5) (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - DAB and NDF (4 of 5) (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - DAB and NDF (5 of 5) (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Marshall Project (1 of 6) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Marshall Project (2 of 6) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Marshall Project (3 of 6) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Marshall Project (4 of 6) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Marshall Project (5 of 6) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Marshall Project (6 of 6) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Mirante, Edith; Project Maje (1 of 11) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Mirante, Edith; Project Maje (2 of 11) (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Mirante, Edith; Project Maje (3 of 11) (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Mirante, Edith; Project Maje (4 of 11) (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Mirante, Edith; Project Maje (5 of 11) (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Mirante, Edith; Project Maje (6 of 11) (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Mirante, Edith; Project Maje (7 of 11) (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Mirante, Edith; Project Maje (8 of 11) (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Mirante, Edith; Project Maje (9 of 11) (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Mirante, Edith; Project Maje (10 of 11) (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Mirante, Edith; Project Maje (11 of 11) (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Palaungs (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Sen, Malcolm K. (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Sein TU (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Singapore American School (1 of 7) (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Singapore American School (2 of 7) (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Singapore American School (3 of 7) (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Singapore American School (4 of 7) (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Singapore American School (5 of 7) (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Singapore American School (6 of 7) (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Singapore American School (7 of 7) (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - SLORC National Convention (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Taylor, Robert H. (1 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Taylor, Robert H. (2 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Taylor, Robert H. (3 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - T.R.C. (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - U Nu (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Unpublished Essays (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Burma Socialist Program Party; Constitution of BSPP (1 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Burma Socialist Program Party; BSPP Report, 1966 Seminar (2 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Burma Socialist Program Party; Burma Research Material, Period 1912-1988 (3 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Burma Socialist Program Party; National Unity Policy, 1964 (4 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - History of Burma (1 of 2), 1932-1952 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - History of Burma (2 of 2), 1932-1952 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - World War II and Burmese Independence, 1940’s (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Office of War Informational Memo on “Burmese Personality”, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1950’s-1960’s (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1950’s-1960’s (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Personal Letters and Correspondence (1 of 8), 1950’s-1960’s (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Personal Letters and Correspondence (2 of 8), 1950’s-1960’s (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Personal Letters and Correspondence (3 of 8), 1950’s-1960’s (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Personal Letters and Correspondence (4 of 8), 1950’s-1960’s (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Personal Letters and Correspondence (5 of 8), 1950’s-1960’s (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Personal Letters and Correspondence (6 of 8), 1950’s-1960’s (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Personal Letters and Correspondence (7 of 8), 1950’s-1960’s (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Personal Letters and Correspondence (8 of 8), 1950’s-1960’s (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Public Administration in Burma, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Furnnall Course Notes (1 of 2), 1955 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Furnnall Course Notes (2 of 2), 1955 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Journal Articles and Book Reviews (1 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Journal Articles and Book Reviews (2 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Election Documents, Voting Slips, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Role of Transportation in the Economic Development of Burma (1 of 2), 1956 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Role of Transportation in the Economic Development of Burma (2 of 2), 1956 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Marshall Wright Original Manuscript on Burma Foreign Relations (1 of 2), 1958 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Marshall Wright Original Manuscript on Burma Foreign Relations (2 of 2), 1958 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Shan State Rebellion: Photos of Shan Leaders in Uprising [photos], 1958 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Wesleyan University Correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Sao Sai Mong Paper for Cornell Seminar, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Columbia University on Modern East Asia: Japan, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence (1 of 5), 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence (2 of 5), 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence (3 of 5), 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence (4 of 5), 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence (5 of 5), 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence (1 of 5), 1966 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence (2 of 5), 1966 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence (3 of 5), 1966 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence (4 of 5), 1966 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence (5 of 5), 1966 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence (1 of 4), 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence (2 of 4), 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence (3 of 4), 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence (4 of 4), 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Education and Politics in Burma, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Manuscript Notes, 1967/1972 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Panel Asia Association Meeting, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence (1 of 5), 1968 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence (2 of 5), 1968 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence (3 of 5), 1968 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence (4 of 5), 1968 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence (5 of 5), 1968 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Dee Hall, Cornell Courses, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Essay Notes, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Lectures (1 of 3), 1968 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Lectures (2 of 3), 1968 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Lectures (3 of 3), 1968 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Asian Association Meeting (1 of 4), 1969 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Asian Association Meeting (2 of 4), 1969 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Asian Association Meeting (3 of 4), 1969 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Asian Association Meeting (4 of 4), 1969 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (1 of 6), 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (2 of 6), 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (3 of 6), 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence (4 of 6), 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (5 of 6), 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence (6 of 6), 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Second Burma Constitution (1 of 2), 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Second Burma Constitution (2 of 2), 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence (1 of 5), 1972 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence (2 of 5), 1972 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence (3 of 5), 1972 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence (4 of 5), 1972 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence (5 of 5), 1972 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Papers for ISEAS Conference: New Direction in the International Relations of Southeast Asia (1 of 7), 1972 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Papers for ISEAS Conference: New Direction in the International Relations of Southeast Asia (2 of 7), 1972 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Papers for ISEAS Conference: New Direction in the International Relations of Southeast Asia (3 of 7), 1972 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Papers for ISEAS Conference: New Direction in the International Relations of Southeast Asia (4 of 7), 1972 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Papers for ISEAS Conference: New Direction in the International Relations of Southeast Asia (5 of 7), 1972 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Papers for ISEAS Conference: New Direction in the International Relations of Southeast Asia (6 of 7), 1972 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Papers for ISEAS Conference: New Direction in the International Relations of Southeast Asia (7 of 7), 1972 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Process of Communication in Modernization of Rural Society, A Survey Report on Two Burmese Villages, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - U Nu’s Revolt Against Ne Win, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - 1973 Census, Socialist Republic of the Union of Burma (1 of 3), 1973 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - 1973 Census, Socialist Republic of the Union of Burma (2 of 3), 1973 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - 1973 Census, Socialist Republic of the Union of Burma (3 of 3), 1973 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1973-1980 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1973-1980 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Various Newspaper Clippings on Burma ( 1 of 2), 1974 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Various Newspaper Clippings on Burma ( 2 of 2), 1974 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence (1 of 4), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence (2 of 4), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence (3 of 4), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence (4 of 4), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence (1 of 5), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence (2 of 5), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence (3 of 5), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence (4 of 5), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence (5 of 5), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Indians in Burma, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - U Thant Commemoration Symposium, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence (1 of 5), 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence (2 of 5), 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence (3 of 5), 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence (4 of 5), 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence (5 of 5), 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence (1 of 6), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (2 of 6), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (3 of 6), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (4 of 6), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (5 of 6), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (6 of 6), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (1 of 4), 1979 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (2 of 4), 1979 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (3 of 4), 1979 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (4 of 4), 1979 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Fullbright (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Fullbright (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - SSRC Travel Grant, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Burma Interviews, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence (1 of 6), 1981 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence (2 of 6), 1981 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence (3 of 6), 1981 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence (4 of 6), 1981 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence (5 of 6), 1981 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence (6 of 6), 1981 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Silverstein Article Submissions, 1984-1994 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Various Manuscripts (1 of 3), 1985 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Various Manuscripts (2 of 3), 1985 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Various Manuscripts (3 of 3), 1985 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Manuscripts (1 of 3), 1986 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Manuscripts (2 of 3), 1986 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Manuscripts (3 of 3), 1986 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Bonn Conference (1 of 4), 1988 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Bonn Conference (2 of 4), 1988 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Bonn Conference (3 of 4), 1988 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Bonn Conference (4 of 4), 1988 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Defense Intelligence Conference (1 of 5), 1988 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Defense Intelligence Conference (2 of 5), 1988 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Defense Intelligence Conference (3 of 5), 1988 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Defense Intelligence Conference (4 of 5), 1988 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Defense Intelligence Conference (5 of 5), 1988 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Paper by Jean Louis Conne, “The Karenni Cry”, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 39)